<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>leibniz*</title>
		<description>il blog di Piero Macchioni</description>		
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Bad time to be on Facebook</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Two things I read last weekend via &lt;a href=&quot;http://mailchi.mp/hackernewsletter/360?e=69e4c56ba1&quot;&gt;Hacker Newsletter&lt;/a&gt; about Facebook manners and limits (and our manners and limits).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blakewatson.com/journal/why-i-left-facebook&quot;&gt;Blake Watson: Why I left Facebook&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Over time, we’ve become hooked on the social validation Facebook (and other services) provide. Before I hit the delete button on my account, one of the last things that kept me on Facebook—after I had largely stopped posting and reading the News Feed—was simply checking my notifications. I unconsciously craved that little hit of happiness one gets when they see, So-and-so liked your post. But that’s not real happiness. It’s an unhealthy addiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://boffosocko.com/2017/07/11/the-facebook-algorithm-mom-problem/&quot;&gt;Chris Aldrich: The Facebook Algorithm Mom Problem&lt;/a&gt;, or How I temporarily cut my mom out of my social media life to reach a larger audience:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;mom-autolike (n.)&lt;/strong&gt;  When a mother automatically clicks “like” on a piece of content posted to social media by one of their children, not because it has any inherent value, but simply because the content came from their child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PS: This post is also a webmention test. Feedback appreciated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_&lt;br /&gt;
possed → &lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-twitter&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/leibniz/status/886704768416186368&quot;&gt;@leibniz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/openweb/2017/07/16/Bad-time-to-be-on-Facebook/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/openweb/2017/07/16/Bad-time-to-be-on-Facebook/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Let's Save Net Neutrality</title>
				<description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Net neutrality is the principle that Internet providers should not control what we see and do online. The rules prohibit Internet providers from blocking, throttling, and paid prioritization—”fast lanes” - for sites that pay, and slow lanes for everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/&quot;&gt;Battle for the web&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/07/todays-day-lets-save-net-neutrality&quot;&gt;Let’s Save Net Neutrality&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span rel=&quot;syndication&quot; class=&quot;u-syndication&quot;&gt;_&lt;br /&gt;
possed → &lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-twitter&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/leibniz/status/885040901537574912&quot;&gt;@leibniz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/openweb/2017/07/12/Save-Net-Neutrality/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/openweb/2017/07/12/Save-Net-Neutrality/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The new electric spring of the News River</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/electric-river.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;electric-river&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One week ago in Perugia, during the annual Journalism Festival, &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com&quot;&gt;Dave Winer&lt;/a&gt; talked about journos taking back their online distribution system, now firmly in silos’ hands (blue silos, big F, you got it). He called that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.festivaldelgiornalismo.com/programme/2017/plan-b-making-a-home-for-news-on-the-open-web&quot;&gt;Plan B&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First step, he said, forget your readers for a moment and start your own News River. It is something he’s been working on for years, basically a feed aggregator with no fancy stuff. It is radical because, when you use it, you just see what your sources publish when they do it: no algorithms, no distracting images, no ads. It’s like newsrooms in the old times, with the AP feed on your monitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m simplifying but the old News River needed a server, a bit of programming and a few bucks to let everything run. Why bother if you have amazing free products like &lt;a href=&quot;https://feedly.com/&quot;&gt;Feedly&lt;/a&gt;? So now Dave shipped &lt;a href=&quot;http://rss2.io/electric/&quot;&gt;Electric River&lt;/a&gt;, a Mac app easily customizable - well, you can enjoy more if you know some coding - you can run on your desktop with no cost at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I’d be naive if I thought Electric River was that easy. I still think it has a steep learning curve for the average journalist (at least here in Italy).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically you have to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Run a Mac.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Know what rss feeds are.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be able to get them from your favorite sources.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have some favorite sources.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mix your sources so you don’t have too much information, aka too much noise.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be happy with the super basic OPML editor Dave provided, or tweak your rivers building a few tabs (which I did)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be happy with no images, no embedded videos, no automagical hierarchy, no likes, comments, retweets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All considered I’m good with all the stuff above. But I’d really like some improvements to make Electric River not just a techie smart app but an app a journalist could use more at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;actual-improvements&quot;&gt;ACTUAL IMPROVEMENTS&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;some kind of pagination: because if you’ve been away for a while, you lose too much news.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;search: I’d start with some &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cmd + F&lt;/code&gt; for searching the page, but a search box would be amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;stars/readitlater: some kind of selecting items so you can work them later or just remember.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;synch: Electric River is totally desktop, but our lives are mobile and multi-device. Some kind of feed memory would help.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;sharing: Dave offers his awesome &lt;a href=&quot;http://radio3.io/&quot;&gt;Radio3&lt;/a&gt; for tweeting and posting on Facebook. I’d love some more customization for sharing directly in Instapaper, Pinboard, Slack etc…&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All of the above functions are already available from Feedly, Feedbin, etc…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ui-stuff&quot;&gt;UI STUFF&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’d really could use a “Return to Top” arrow.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’d love to change the default font, text size, and background (like you can on Kindle or Instapaper).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is my feedback after one week. Electric River is only 0.40e, so it has still to grow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/journalism/2017/04/15/what-is-Electric-River/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journalism/2017/04/15/what-is-Electric-River/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Un anno di &quot;Lo leggo dopo&quot;</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/refuel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;refuel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purtroppo anche quest’anno non sono riuscito a usare un solo sistema per salvare articoli e post in maniera organica. Ma come nel 2015 ho continuato a usare una ricetta di &lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com/discover&quot;&gt;IF&lt;/a&gt; che permette di formattare in modo abbastanza decente tutto quello che salvo su &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instapaper.com/&quot;&gt;Instapaper&lt;/a&gt;. Non è tutto-tutto quello che salvo allo scopo di una lettura successiva (vero Feedly? vero Pinboard?), ma lo sparpagliamento inorganico è parte della mia identità digitale, credo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;È stato l’anno di un sacco di gente, ma io qui trovo molto Donald Trump, intelligenze artificiali, Francesco Totti, Slack, Ed Snowden, Bullet Journaling, molto Il Post e il fantastico dibattito liberal sulla post-verità, che poi sono le “minchiate”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Zjdic8&quot;&gt;Employee benefits at Basecamp — Signal v. Noise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our headquarters in Chicago.Employee benefits at BasecampI’m often asked about the benefits we offer at Basecamp. Potential…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/231Zzpr&quot;&gt;Axel Springer’s Bild is testing news delivery via Facebook Messenger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Axel Springer’s Bild is testing news delivery via Facebook Messenger » Nieman Journalism Lab Fellowships Reports Lab Storyboard Nieman Foundation at Harvard…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Qe0sWJ&quot;&gt;Repubblica e il mondo che vogliamo raccontare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RvpPEA&quot;&gt;27 anni alla fine dei giornali di carta - cheFare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niente panico, il titolo è una provocazione. Se i quotidiani cartacei sono davvero fatalmente destinati all’estinzione, allora, tenendo conto del ritmo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SteJ3i&quot;&gt;Modelli di giornalismo - Tre direttori a confronto - Slow News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(*) L’analisi che segue prescinde completamente da qualsiasi considerazione relativa a idee politiche o linea editoriale e si concentra esclusivamente sulle…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1JlthiD&quot;&gt;A Note from the Editor, William McKenzie via The Catalyst&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first edition of The Catalyst: A Journal of Ideas from the Bush Institute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1PkRN5Y&quot;&gt;We Don’t Live in the World We Were Born Into, an Essay by Mark Cuban via The Catalyst&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As owner, Mark Cuban embraced change after the Dallas Mavericks lost in the NBA Finals in 2006 to the Miami Heat. The revamped roster and coaching staff brought…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1P9RSrd&quot;&gt;The sky is falling on print newspapers faster than you think — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last October, a McKinsey report declared, “We believe that many of the people likely to abandon print newspapers and print consumer magazines have already done…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QLqqkC&quot;&gt;The End of Twitter - The New Yorker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter might rebound in the wake of Jack Dorsey’s reappointment as C.E.O., but the service is still in trouble. Credit Photograph by Richard Drew / AP It…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SYeehX&quot;&gt;7 cose (belle) che succedono quando il capo non controlla — In italiano&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Mamma, il giornale che stai leggendo è già stampato?
– Sì
– Allora perché lo correggi?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1K109O1&quot;&gt;New York Times Co. Announces Newsroomwide Strategy Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buoyed by strong digital growth and cost savings, The New York Times Company reported on Thursday an increase in quarterly profit but said revenue was flat as…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SxuoiI&quot;&gt;The New York Times’ new Slack 2016 election bot sends readers’ questions straight to the newsroom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want more election coverage right in your company’s Slack? On Friday, The New York Times rolled out NYT Election Bot, which anyone can add to their Slack…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1KxRanu&quot;&gt;Here’s how Twitter’s new algorithmic timeline is going to work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can opt out Twitter went into an uproar Friday after a BuzzFeed report that the social network was on the brink introducing an algorithmic, more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1ThJAA8&quot;&gt;La cosa più bella di “Zoolander 2” sono le recensioni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoolander 2 è il nuovo film scritto, diretto e interpretato da Ben Stiller. È nei cinema dall’11 febbraio ed è il sequel di Zoolander, uscito nel 2001. Il primo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QaOmc9&quot;&gt;Review: What It’s Like to Have Super Hearing Abilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile With Here earbuds from Doppler Labs, you’re in control of your aural environment, and it’s pretty sweet. February 12, 2016 Sponsored by I never thought…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/20B7G8s&quot;&gt;How BuzzFeed’s Jonah Peretti Is Building A 100-Year Media Company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BuzzFeed publisher Dao Nguyen, Motion Pictures president Ze Frank, and CEO Jonah Peretti keep BuzzFeed weird—and powerful—by never getting too comfortable.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1KPEpVy&quot;&gt;Wolff: Print’s dead — but so is digital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man reads the newspaper ‘Financial Times’ at the 46th Annual Meeting of the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland Jan. 22, 2016.(Photo: Jean-christophe…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1LubAci&quot;&gt;Speciali - Dream Theater: il track-by-track di “The Astonishing”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’attesa è quasi finita: fra due settimane sarà out l’ultima fatica discografica dei Dream Theater, dopo un disco dai giudizi contrastanti e con l’oramai…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1XAtDo5&quot;&gt;Upgrade Your iPhone Passcode To Defeat the FBI’s Backdoor Strategy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Apple CEO Tim Cook published an open letter opposing a court order to build the FBI a “backdoor” for the iPhone. Cook wrote that the backdoor, which…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2175oDw&quot;&gt;La squadra di calcio danese che sceglie i giocatori come in “Moneyball”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In una delle partite di andata dei sedicesimi di finale di Europa League, la semisconosciuta squadra danese del Midtjylland ha sorprendentemente sconfitto 2 a 1…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1XG73dD&quot;&gt;Universities and the open web&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mentioned in an earlier post that I visited the MIT Media Lab on the 11th of Feb. It was a great trip, just one day back and forth. I wanted to see the Media…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RW8Efb&quot;&gt;Matteo Renzi’s naughty inner child&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1oNnQQ8&quot;&gt;The Weird Global Appeal of Heavy Metal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s “world music” isn’t Peruvian pan flutes or African talking drums. It’s loud guitars, growling vocals and ultrafast “blast” beats. Heavy metal has become…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1qNzJ7g&quot;&gt;How Working on Multiple Screens Can Actually Help You Focus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben Wiseman In her role at MaRS Discovery District, a startup incubator in Toronto, Karen Schulman Dupuis reads 10,000 to 15,000 words a day onscreen. But she…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1TCPVqf&quot;&gt;How to Think About Bots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A botifestoWe live in a world of bots. Generally speaking, these sets of algorithms are responsible for so much on the backend of the internet, from making…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1LwvIzK&quot;&gt;The Future of Chat Isn’t AI — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instant interaction is keyAt Kik, we’ve been thinking about the coming bot revolution for a long time. We first launched a basic bot platform a year and a half…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1VYIGqp&quot;&gt;Unfundable Slack bots — Free Code Camp — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In December, Slack announced a $80 million fund to invest in software projects that complement its technology. As an early adopter of the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QykfjB&quot;&gt;The tactical networking guide for introverts — Free Code Camp — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tactical networking guide for introvertsWhy am I writing a guide about networking for introverts?There are three questions within this question: why write…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1X27cak&quot;&gt;Come ha fatto Trump a diventare Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Durante la campagna elettorale per le primarie americane si è detto molto sulla carriera imprenditoriale di Donald Trump: si è parlato delle sue dichiarazioni…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1R1l2Fz&quot;&gt;The Risk I Will Not Take&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Americans today face a profound challenge to preserve our common values and national promise.Wage stagnation at home and our declining influence abroad have…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1U88vFt&quot;&gt;Facebook is eating the world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illustration: AP Something really dramatic is happening to our media landscape, the public sphere, and our journalism industry, almost without us noticing and…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1YgzAqv&quot;&gt;Capire Snapchat — In italiano — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perché non è solo un’applicazione di “messaggistica istantanea”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1pu8zEt&quot;&gt;Newsonomics: The New York Times re-invents Page One — and it’s better than print ever was&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah, the art of the broadsheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;march-8-2016-at-1236am&quot;&gt;March 8, 2016 at 12:36AM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1W7YBTE&quot;&gt;Google’s AI Wins First Game in Historic Match With Go Champion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA — After an extraordinarily close contest, Google’s artificially intelligent Go-playing computer system has beaten Lee Sedol, one of the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1YCJgfk&quot;&gt;Mi manda Arrigo Sacchi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Da difensore (scarso) del Parma alla guida di Fendi. Storia contromano di Pietro Beccari, ex calciatore, che ha messo insieme Anita…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RzugJD&quot;&gt;4 cose che i giornali pensano di BuzzFeed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ricerca sui media • by Philip Di Salvo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1YFxhOa&quot;&gt;Marty Baron: Loss of public trust is journalism’s greatest challenge - World News Publishing Focus by WAN-IFRA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He shared his views on the current state of journalism and his concerns and hopes for the profession with the World Editors Forum. How do you see the future of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UUXAjp&quot;&gt;The future of computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The era of predictable improvement in computer hardware is ending. What comes next? IN 1971 the fastest car in the world was the Ferrari Daytona, capable of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1U4S9yO&quot;&gt;When You Listen to Music, You’re Never Alone - Issue 34: Adaptation - Nautilus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a late spring evening in 2015, at South Street Seaport, a square on the southern tip of Manhattan, hundreds of people slipped on headphones and slipped into…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1U4gzIM&quot;&gt;This Is What I Do Before 8 AM. — Life Learning — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo credit: Mikesh Kaos — http://ift.tt/24X7wxc Is What I Do Before 8 AM.Don’t try and life-hack your way to post human status.I’m an…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/22kzuEg&quot;&gt;Perché la vittoria di AlphaGo è importante&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AlphaGo , l’intelligenza artificiale (AI) di Google DeepMind , ha battuto il campione mondiale del complicato gioco da tavolo Go in una serie di partite molto…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;march-16-2016-at-0713pm&quot;&gt;March 16, 2016 at 07:13PM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QVLNQ8&quot;&gt;How to Make Twitter Actually Useful&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the longer-than-140-character version&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;march-16-2016-at-0813pm&quot;&gt;March 16, 2016 at 08:13PM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QRAGGF&quot;&gt;Everything You Know About Artificial Intelligence is Wrong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isaac Asimov’s Three Laws of Robotics won’t be nearly enough to control AI. Robots of Dawn cover by Michael Whelan It was hailed as the most significant test of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/24DsgcZ&quot;&gt;How Snapchat Built a Business By Confusing Olds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Max Chafkin &amp;amp; Sarah Frier March 3, 2016 Photographs by Julian Berman Advertisers want the $16 billion social network’s young users from Bloomberg…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Mam7im&quot;&gt;Here’s the Full Transcript of TIME’s Interview With Apple CEO Tim Cook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook sat down with TIME’s Nancy Gibbs and Lev Grossman on March 10 to discuss his company’s rapidly escalating fight with the FBI over encryption.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1nS5A77&quot;&gt;Netlify: Interview with Parker Moore from Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there is a constantly growing roster of static web tools available for developers of both the professional and amateur stripe, none swings as much weight…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/25bf0N7&quot;&gt;What Happens When Millennials Run the Workplace? - NYTimes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joel Pavelski, 27, isn’t the first person who has lied to his boss to scam some time off work. But inventing a friend’s funeral, when in fact he was building a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Shp5AU&quot;&gt;Bartlet for president! The new West Wing podcast is a tonic to Trumpmania&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s time to revisit the West Wing … the original show was an antidote to the Bush years, and the podcast will be a tonic for the ‘mad circus’ of politics…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1WOXUyH&quot;&gt;How to Make a Bot That Isn’t Racist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day after Microsoft launched its “AI teen girl Twitter chatbot,” Twitter taught her to be racist . Really, really racist. Screencap via @geraldmellor . The…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1pYfgPp&quot;&gt;A Conversation on Privacy — The Intercept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The balance between national security and government intrusion on the rights of private citizens will be the topic of a panel discussion featuring renowned…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1nymBTT&quot;&gt;An Introvert’s Guide to Networking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Networking events are nerve-wracking enough to make anyone self-conscious, but they’re particularly difficult for introverts, says Dr. Bernardo J. Carducci,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1PBMIQb&quot;&gt;Your Desk Is A Drug&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care about your productive space — I care about your productive mindset. I’m in a laundromat. It smells like cat urine and old people. We had to pass on…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1tWMb2o&quot;&gt;Defining a microblog post - Manton Reece&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m working on a new project around timelines and microblogs. It consumes RSS feeds, so I’ve been wondering how strict to be when accepting posts. What does…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UC4BXK&quot;&gt;Behind the scenes: How we run our podcast called “The Distance” — Signal v. Noise — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommended by Jason Fried and Jason Fried 20 hrs ago 5 min read Recommended by Jason Fried and Behind the scenes: How we run our podcast called “The Distance”…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1ofsXb0&quot;&gt;Searching For Google CEO Sundar Pichai, The Most Powerful Tech Giant You’ve Never Heard Of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Consumer Electronics Show, universally known as CES, is a riot of technology. Held annually in the bleak Nevada desert town of Las Vegas, it is a great…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/20tj1qS&quot;&gt;Still Rendering — Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still Rendering My dad sent me 1,936 emails between 2008 and 2015. Most were brief and business-oriented, even when the business was pleasure: “got tix for you,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UWGMcK&quot;&gt;Shorter isn’t better, photos aren’t always alluring and deep digging pays off, recent report concludes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After two years work analyzing more than 400,000 stories, the American Press Institute is beginning to find general patterns in what works to attract and hold…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1MH9ziU&quot;&gt;Colori che svaniscono. Intervista a Elio&amp;amp;leStorieTese&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Share: Mi spiace iniziare con Sanremo, però mi serve per certe cose che voglio chiedervi. A mente fredda, un po’ di settimane dopo, si può dire che per voi…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RYtw0G&quot;&gt;3 takeaways about audience engagement from #ONALondon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting audiences to engage with stories is important to all media organisations, but this process can have different nuances for…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/225vvWy&quot;&gt;La più grande impresa del calcio moderno&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quel video lo avete visto, probabilmente, anche se non ve ne ricordate: circolò moltissimo sui social network e le tv. Era il 12 maggio del 2013, 96esimo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/203K2CR&quot;&gt;Cruciani: ‘La maratona? una grande forma di egoismo ma mi ha aiutato a concentrarmi sul lavoro’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;«Ho sempre corso fin da ragazzino. Avevo una passione per l’ atletica leggera, per le gare dei 5mila e…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SxWKnB&quot;&gt;Making Medium More Powerful for Publishers — The Story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Medium, we’re building out a new corner of the Internet specifically designed for people and publishers who want to experience a deeper level of discourse…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1TAJNvT&quot;&gt;The Web We Have to Save — Matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web We Have to Save The rich, diverse, free web that I loved — and spent years in an Iranian jail for — is dying. Why is nobody stopping it? By Hossein…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/22lVwRM&quot;&gt;Medium and Twitter founder: ‘We put junk food in front of them and they eat it’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter and Medium founder Ev WilliamsPhotograph: Tim Knox Ev Williams is not a fan of the increasingly homogenised media he currently sees, with its emphasis…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1VVmr6M&quot;&gt;Twitter has outsized influence, but it doesn’t drive much traffic for most news orgs, a new report says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April 13, 2016, 12:11 p.m. Audience &amp;amp; Social Twitter has outsized influence, but it doesn’t drive much traffic for most news orgs, a new report says LINK :…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1EVTEYB&quot;&gt;How to Pick Up Girls: A Guide by Girls for Boys - VICE - United States&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spend too much time on the internet and you’ll end up thinking young men today fall into one of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1r8Z92c&quot;&gt;Dieci cose imperdibili da mangiare a New York : IL Magazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1r87mUf&quot;&gt;Media Websites Battle Faltering Ad Revenue and Traffic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The business of online news has never been forgiving. But in recent weeks, what had been a simmering worry among publishers has turned. This month, Mashable, a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SvQLT5&quot;&gt;I Sent A Silly Tweet About Italian TV And Became Internet Famous In Italy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I was in Italy a few weeks ago for a journalism festival . One night I was out to dinner and couldn’t stop staring at the TV. There was a show on that was…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/262JRvA&quot;&gt;The Minecraft Generation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan wanted to build an unpredictable trap. An 11-year-old in dark horn-­rimmed glasses, Jordan is a devotee of Minecraft, the computer game in which you…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1XqEgcS&quot;&gt;The Gaunt Life: My Sub-Elite Life with an Elite Girlfriend: LA Marathon, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the first in a series of entries on my life as a sub-elite runner with an elite girlfriend. My partner is a talented, respected distance runner on the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SIiMKk&quot;&gt;Chi è il più grande guerriero di Game of Thrones?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un tabellone, un torneo, una discussione. Volendo, potreste anche vederla come una Coppa del Mondo delle Mazzate di Westeros. Si può dire di tutto di Game of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UcQXJh&quot;&gt;Your Media Business Will Not Be Saved&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A still from John Carpenter’s “Prince of Darkness” (it’s actually about Satan but whatever) Video will not save your media business. Nor will bots, newsletters,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/26qKmzR&quot;&gt;‘She has a name’: Amazon’s Alexa is a sleeper hit, with serious superfans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users of Amazon’s Echo, which respond to the voice command ‘Alexa’, seem to buy it out of curiosity and slowly adopt it into their lives.Photograph:…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SQcbNX&quot;&gt;The Internet Really Has Changed Everything. Here’s the Proof. — Backchannel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How have decades of mass media and technology changed us? A writer returns to his remote hometown — once isolated, now connected. And finds unexpected answers.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1WDDAlC&quot;&gt;Dilly ding, dilly dong, il Leicester è campione d’Inghilterra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La squadra di Ranieri è stata in testa così a lungo che tutti hanno potuto raccontare la propria versione della “favola”, da quella sul collettivo antiliberista…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1r8h3BF&quot;&gt;Come nasce il giornale più bello del mondo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;01 maggio 2016 11:19 La lezione di italiano è il lunedì. Andrea, l’insegnante, un ragazzo alto di 37 anni originario di Catania e trapiantato negli Stati Uniti,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Tj1fm9&quot;&gt;I giornalisti stanno uccidendo il giornalismo?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La scelta del New York Times di nominare Jim Rutenberg come nuovo responsabile della sezione media è stata una mossa intelligente. L’ultimo articolo di…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1T04WQJ&quot;&gt;Apple Stole My Music. No, Seriously.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The software is functioning as intended,” said Amber. “Wait,” I asked, “so it’s supposed to delete my personal files from my internal hard drive without asking…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/24BRdok&quot;&gt;Chatbots Are Your Newest, Dumbest Co-Workers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Getty Images Source: Aspect Starting this July, when customer service employees at Overstock.com are too sick to come to work, they’ll tell Mila…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1T6VI58&quot;&gt;Former Facebook Workers: We Routinely Suppressed Conservative News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook workers routinely suppressed news stories of interest to conservative readers from the social network’s influential “trending”…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/277c30X&quot;&gt;The Facebook Papers, Part 1: The great unbundling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the first in a four-part series looking at what happens when what you do is now done by someone else.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/277c2KB&quot;&gt;Inside Evan Spiegel’s very private Snapchat Story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Evan Spiegel was Evan Spiegel , there were times he wanted to fit in. Like in June 2012, when Spiegel walked across a makeshift stage erected inside…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UMr9E5&quot;&gt;25 years later, Walt Mossberg says technology is still too hard to use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology is reshaping every industry and Recode is changing to reflect that. But as this site moves into a new era, it’s a good time to remember how quickly…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Yi4cYC&quot;&gt;What Will GitHub Be in 5 years?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GitHub has had a profound effect on software, and therefore the world. Everyone knows the company that has raised a lot of money…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1OdSf5T&quot;&gt;Chi sono i ghostwriter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;«Qualche mese fa sono andata a una festa per l’uscita di un libro di una mia autrice», dice Francesca Parravicini, ghostwriter, «e all’improvviso mi sono…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1OpNpx6&quot;&gt;A long talk with Facebook about its role in journalism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy birthday, Instant Articles! A year ago today, Facebook introduced Instant Articles — a quick-loading news format, hosted on Facebook’s own servers, that…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1O5Vyfl&quot;&gt;Come Amazon ha creato Echo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’idea di dover dire a Jeff Bezos che ha torto mette sempre un po’ di paura. Nell’autunno del 2014, tuttavia, un gruppetto di persone che stavano lavorando allo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1sqhnNo&quot;&gt;How the New York Times plans to conquer the world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;POLITICO EUROPE Brussels The Continent Policy Brussels Playbook Morning Exchange Morgen Europa Brussels Influence Morning Trade Morning Agriculture &amp;amp; Food…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1XMNxOJ&quot;&gt;This Week’s Worst Person in Westeros: Bran Stark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not even Max Von Sydow wants to look him the eye. HBO After each episode in Game of Thrones Season 6, we’ll be answering a crucial question: Who is currently…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1sc3kKY&quot;&gt;How Diane Arbus Became ‘Arbus’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diane and Allan Arbus in 1950. Frances McLaughlin-Gill/Condé Nast, via Getty Images Diane Arbus was teetering on the edge of a breakdown. In 1956, she tearfully…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1P2VGww&quot;&gt;The fall of Salon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former CEO Cindy Jeffers. - Salon A Facebook page dedicated to celebrating the 20th anniversary of digital media pioneer Salon is functioning as a crowdsourced…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RRFnx3&quot;&gt;Tegan and Sara, Scientists of the Love Song&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tegan and Sara, Scientists of the Love Song&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1RAoCGH&quot;&gt;Why You Will Marry the Wrong Person&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marion Fayolle IT’S one of the things we are most afraid might happen to us. We go to great lengths to avoid it. And yet we do it all the same: We marry the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/22CzRXc&quot;&gt;Il pane e le rose. Ecco il ritorno della madre perfetta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lunedì 06 Giugno 2016 “Il Figlio”, lo speciale di Annalena Benini che racconta i figli, i genitori, i figli degli altri. Scrivete tutto quello che vi passa per…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1TTJXNM&quot;&gt;People are falling in love with a simple productivity system that just uses pen and paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m one of those people who is constantly testing out new productivity apps in the hopes that this is the technology that will transform my life for good. Each…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/22MPP0M&quot;&gt;The Future of Podcasting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like driving, even if I end up sitting in traffic. I enjoy doing the laundry, and take my time folding shirts just so. I volunteer to wash the dishes. After…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/23984xA&quot;&gt;Digital News Report 2016: smartphone, algoritmi e Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15 giugno 2016 • Editoria , In evidenza •by Philip Di Salvo Distributed content , ad-blocking , video e smartphone. Se si dovesse fare una foto di gruppo alle…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UeOqzT&quot;&gt;The Forrest Gump of the Internet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To a certain kind of nerd, Ev Williams is the Forrest Gump of internet media. Williams helped write the software that made us call blogs blogs . He founded a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/28Lc1UD&quot;&gt;Be Prepared: We’re Entering A Post-Device Era&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Inc. CEO Steve Jobs holds up the new iPad as he speaks during an Apple Special Event at Yerba Buena Center for the Arts January 27, 2010, in San…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/21tsZdl&quot;&gt;Apple doesn’t understand photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most innovative thing Apple did with their Photo app recently was the addition of a ‘Selfie’ filter. You can find the folder in your Photos app, and yeah,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/28Y8yp8&quot;&gt;Cari ragazzi, l’Europa è vostra: non lasciate vincere i venditori di paure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La febbre di oggi è la semplificazione&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/28SNmi7&quot;&gt;Tony Blair: Brexit’s Stunning Coup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10 Downing Street on Friday morning. Ben Stansall/Agence France-Presse — Getty Images London — THE decision of British voters in Thursday’s referendum to leave…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/NZaJJN&quot;&gt;All about ekiben, Japanese train station bentos - Just Bento&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(First off, my apologies for the long silence around here. I’ve been terribly sick since getting back from Japan last week, due to a bad cold that I seem to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/297XmAR&quot;&gt;Now that tech more or less owns the news distribution system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing that’s really spooky about the news distribution system being owned by the tech industry is this — We don’t know who they are really, or what their…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/290YAOn&quot;&gt;What media companies don’t want you to know about ad blockers - Columbia Journalism Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New York Times CEO Mark Thompson caused a minor stir a couple weeks ago when he gave a speech at an advertising conference declaring that “No one who refuses to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/28LEDgM&quot;&gt;Who owns the news consumer: Social media platforms or publishers? - Columbia Journalism Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image: AP Editor’s note: The full discussion of this research can be found here . The relationship between news organizations and platform companies has become…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/299l5k8&quot;&gt;Esino Lario ha fatto “Modifica”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;«Mi sono perso», dice Felix Nartey. Ha 26 anni, lavora in banca ed è il “community manager” della sezione ghanese di Wikipedia. Lo dice guardando perplesso un…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29hYUKN&quot;&gt;Consigli per gli acquisti - Wittgenstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benché al Post tendiamo a leggere le sue quotidiane invettive apocalittiche con una certa supponente condiscendenza , le questioni che pone Massimo Mantellini…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29y8lcz&quot;&gt;News and Facebook - Charlie Rose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full Transcript 00:00 Hari Sreenivasan: Facebook connects over a billion people each day around the world on its social media platform. It has also become…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29W2uLK&quot;&gt;How the internet was invented - Technology - The Guardian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illustration: Danae Diaz at PVUK I n the kingdom of apps and unicorns, Rossotti’s is a rarity. This beer garden in the heart of Silicon Valley has been standing…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29IYDn7&quot;&gt;David Chang’s secret code to unleashing the most amazing flavors on Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David Chang’s Unified Theory of Deliciousness. David Chang runs Momofuku, which includes 13 restaurants, a bakery, two bars, and a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QMzhi2&quot;&gt;David Chang’s Brooklyn Lab Is Making Condiments That Will Revolutionize American Cooking - Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more local news from India, visit Bloombergquint.com Photographer: Tejal Rao/Bloomberg Miso, the fermented soybean paste, has been competing for World’s…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2a1LIeV&quot;&gt;How Sam Esmail Directs the Cast of Mr. Robot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sam Esmail, mid-filming a Mr. Robot scene. Photo: (c) Scott McDermott/USA Portia Doubleday is really tempted to turn her face and stare straight into Michael…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29UXiLl&quot;&gt;Master Plan, Part Deux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first master plan that I wrote 10 years ago is now in the final stages of completion. It wasn’t all that complicated and basically consisted of: Create a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29unqaV&quot;&gt;How Jeff Bezos Is Hurtling Toward World Domination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The clouds surrounding Amazon.com are thickening,” began the Washington Post article by David Streitfeld on February 21, 2001 . In the previous year,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29NUjj6&quot;&gt;Rami Malek of ‘Mr. Robot’: The Face of Hacktivism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rami Malek of “Mr. Robot,” at the Lotte New York Palace. Philip Montgomery for The New York Times Unlike most Hollywood attempts, the computer hacking scenes in…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2axVZ0u&quot;&gt;Facebook 2026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B y nearly any measure, Facebook has had a remarkable year. More than 1.65 billion people use the service every month, making it the world’s largest social…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1T2ys7K&quot;&gt;How I Did It: Kevin Plank of Under Armour (2003 Column) - Inc.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Editor’s Note: To celebrate Inc.’s 35th anniversary, Inc.com is showcasing highlights of our coverage of incredible innovators, risk takers, company builders,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2a7bn2Z&quot;&gt;Jeff Bezos: “Un passo alla volta”, dai libri ai giornali e poi fino alle stelle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeff Bezos: “Un passo alla volta”, dai libri ai giornali e poi fino alle stelle È il suo motto. Ed è proprio così che il fondatore di Amazon ha costruito il suo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2a5RzhK&quot;&gt;Transcript &amp;amp; Video: The Michelle Obama Speech That Brought Down The House At The DNC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, First Lady Michelle Obama delivered an impassioned endorsement of Hillary Clinton at the Democratic National Convention. She…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2a6CcWk&quot;&gt;How to Turn Google Into the Best To-Do App Ever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a certain kind of (slightly uptight) person, it’s easy to spend far more time futzing with your to-do list than actually, you know, doing the things on it.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2aBfsBt&quot;&gt;Transcript: Hillary Clinton’s Speech at the Democratic Convention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hillary Clinton spoke at the Democratic National Convention on Thursday. Damon Winter/The New York Times Following is a transcript of Hillary Clinton ’s address…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2adMvGg&quot;&gt;Twitter’s Fucked&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter’s in trouble. No, I’m not referring to the fact that Twitter’s stock is worth a fraction ofwhat it used to be. Or that its revenue growth is abysmal. Or…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2asGecO&quot;&gt;Meet the Chef Who’s Turning Meat Eaters Into Vegetable Lovers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food It’s not easy to turn generations of meat eaters almost overnight into vegetable lovers. Harder still to do it through a series of surprise-hit cookbooks .…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2b4kf9a&quot;&gt;Someone is wrong on the Internet. That’s where I come in.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SAN DIEGO — In a famous xkcd cartoon , “Duty Calls,” a man’s partner beckons him to bed as he sits alone at…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UUwlpN&quot;&gt;Why I Left My Job In Finance, Turned Off My Phone and Started Living in the Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 35 years, I lived in my head. I focused on to-do lists , skill development and hustling. Professionally, it got me far. But emotionally and spiritually, it…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bisqDQ&quot;&gt;What’s your sidebar personality? — Several People Are Typing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s your sidebar personality? Three people with three ways of managing Slack Illustration by Pete Ryan There is no single way to use Slack. Every team will…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2brMnGR&quot;&gt;Linus Torvalds: “Happy birthday, Linux”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linus Torvalds: “Happy birthday, Linux” Parla l’uomo che nell’agosto di venticinque anni fa cominciò dal cuore del sistema operativo: sviluppò la prima versione…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2c3ViNc&quot;&gt;Maison Labranca, le feste delle idee e lo spumante di plastica a Pantigliate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un giornalista non deve mai usare la prima persona singolare. Qualche volta, con vero o finto pudore, la prima plurale. Questa volta, però, voglio usarla per…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2c0a8UE&quot;&gt;Why Tim Berners-Lee is no friend of Facebook - John Naughton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Zuckerberg, whose aim is to ‘make the world more “connected” but less open’.Photograph: SIPA/Rex/Shutterstock I f there were a Nobel prize for hypocrisy,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bBNTnb&quot;&gt;Digital Marketing Strategy and The Rise of The Micro-Influencer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Campaign image from SLC x Stance featuring Stephanie La Cava Influencers are very much a part of almost any company’s marketing strategy in this day and age.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bBvR94&quot;&gt;Christian Slater on ‘Mr. Robot,’ Escaping a Messy Past, and Ferris Wheels vs. Roller Coasters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrity Christian Slater Isn’t Mr. Robot, He’s Mr. Nice Guy Suit, $895, by Boss - Shirt, $145, by Boss , tie, $200, by Dior Homme , pocket square by Brooks…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bHiJ23&quot;&gt;Come si mandano miliardi di email senza finire nello spam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ogni giorno una società che si chiama MailChimp invia più di un miliardo di email, contenenti informazioni promozionali, pubblicità o newsletter, come quella…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cq9Y9X&quot;&gt;Weiner – how a film about a political sex scandal suddenly got more intimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2c5LQs0&quot;&gt;Exclusive: How Edward Snowden Escaped&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exclusive interview: Edward Snowden lauds “courageous” asylum seekers who sheltered him The covert scheme to dodge U.S. attempts to arrest Snowden…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2czpWy3&quot;&gt;How the Chromebook quietly grew into the machine that’s about to change the computer industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google’s first Chromebook was the kind of laptop you’d design if you didn’t give a damn about laptop design. It was thick, heavy, rubbery, boring, and black.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cvi2Zr&quot;&gt;La storia della foto del “Falling man”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La storia delle stragi dell’11 settembre è un’immensa storia di immagini, riempita a sua volta di mille storie diverse, entrate nella memoria collettiva in una…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1MPY2Zw&quot;&gt;A Massive List of the Best EDC Knives on the Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you got here by typing something like “best EDC knife” into Google, you probably already have a little history with knives. Likely, you already have at least…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cWNr4J&quot;&gt;This man is a big reason why ‘Mr. Robot’ is the first real hacking show on television&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have successfully emailed the post. 9h 128 Kor Adana YouTube/SecureNinja USA Network’s “Mr. Robot” is the first television show to really get hacking right…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cu8QDm&quot;&gt;Review: ‘Snowden,’ Oliver Stone’s Restrained Portrait of a Whistle-Blower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joseph Gordon-Levitt as the title character in Oliver Stone’s “Snowden.” Jürgen Olczyk/Open Road Films Oliver Stone ’s “Snowden,” a quiet, crisply drawn…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cn5y5g&quot;&gt;Italy on the verge of the stupidest censorship law in European history&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a string of high-profile cyberbullying and revenge-porn incidents, the Italian Chamber of Deputies has put forward a bill that will do nothing to prevent…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1YSbggk&quot;&gt;I’m J. Kenji López-Alt of Serious Eats, and This Is How I Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J. Kenji López-Alt is the author of The Food Lab , a column on Serious Eats and now a book which explores cooking with a scientific eye. In fact, the New York…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cAXOMJ&quot;&gt;Andrew Sullivan: My Distraction Sickness — and Yours&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sitting in a large meditation hall in a converted novitiate in central Massachusetts when I reached into my pocket for my iPhone. A woman in the front of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cJvCoK&quot;&gt;‘Snowden’ Isn’t Really About Snowden&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Citizenfour, her Oscar-winning documentary from 2014 , Laura Poitras chronicled the tense, high-stakes first encounter in a Hong Kong hotel room between an…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cQnHbp&quot;&gt;Hillary Clinton for President&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any normal election year, we’d compare the two presidential candidates side by side on the issues. But this is not a normal election year. A comparison like…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1FLCeuj&quot;&gt;You Have Ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You Have Ideas What you need is more bad ideas. You know the drill. It’s late in the morning on Saturday and you’re outside mowing the lawn. Or maybe you don’t…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cWxXib&quot;&gt;The To-Do List and the Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stumbled across an article by CJ Chilvers entitled ‘ Kill Your To Do List ’ that got me thinking about my own task management habits and how to better…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cw0l7Y&quot;&gt;Sacchi esalta Totti: gli è mancato il riconoscimento internazionale che meritava. Colpa della Roma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SACCHI Luca Valdiserri per il “Corriere della Sera” Si sono soltanto sfiorati, ma insieme potevano fare sfracelli. Arrigo Sacchi, l’ allenatore rivoluzionario,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bOw5Kp&quot;&gt;Reinventiamo RSS per non essere dipendenti da Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Al momento Facebook è responsabile di oltre il 40% di tutto il traffico web in entrata delle testate giornalistiche…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cZYQlp&quot;&gt;Con e senza Francesco Totti&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cAzIif&quot;&gt;Il mio Cav.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gli ottant’anni di Silvio Berlusconi nel racconto personale di Giuliano Ferrara. La tivù, il Milan, la politica, le donne, la malattia, l’eterno ritorno e altre…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dqezgG&quot;&gt;Tutto Berlusconi decennio dopo decennio - La Stampa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nasce primogenito il 29 settembre da papà Luigi, impiegato di banca, e mamma Rosa, segretaria del direttore generale della Pirelli.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dtut5t&quot;&gt;Feltri racconta Berlusconi: tre botte alla D’Addario, e quella volta che distrussi il suo cesso&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vittorio Feltri per “Libero Quotidiano”. Antico adagio: l’unico modo per vivere a lungo è invecchiare. Silvio Berlusconi non…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1JgMFgJ&quot;&gt;How to Bullet Journal: The Absolute Ultimate Guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The January air smells like organization. You can’t fight it, so let’s lean into it with lazy genius attitude. I want to tell you about the Bullet Journal. You…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dzTTmf&quot;&gt;Diego Piacentini: “Regalo due anni all’Italia per portarla nella modernità e farvi dimenticare i certificati”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diego Piacentini: “Regalo due anni all’Italia per portarla nella modernità e farvi dimenticare i certificati” L’intervista. Il supermanager di Amazon diventa…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dD1CLt&quot;&gt;People and Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Gall WEAPONS OF MATH DESTRUCTION How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy By Cathy O’Neil 259 pp. Crown, $26. O’Neil’s book offers a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dG8N6g&quot;&gt;Beginning a bullet journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last couple of years, life has gotten very busy. I’ve found myself struggling to find time to do the things I love and failing at remembering to do the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dG24IN&quot;&gt;Behind the Pixel: Google’s First Real Threat to Apple’s iPhone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dZsBly&quot;&gt;What Will Break People’s Addictions to Their Phones?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://politi.co/2eb1yFo&quot;&gt;What If the Newspaper Industry Made a Colossal Mistake?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getty What if almost the entire newspaper industry got it wrong? What if, in the mad dash two decades ago to repurpose and extend editorial content onto the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2eivaUj&quot;&gt;Mossberg: Google’s first phone is first rate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At long last, almost 8 years to the day the first Android phone went on sale, Google is launching a smartphone for which it designed the hardware, software and…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2e2fz98&quot;&gt;Google Pixel Is the Best Phone on the Planet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I write about gadgets, which means everyone asks me what laptop or dishwasher or whatever to buy. I struggle with this, because the answer often starts with,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2e17kZL&quot;&gt;How the Web Became Unreadable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought my eyesight was beginning to go. It turns out, I’m suffering from design. I t’s been getting harder for me to read things on my phone and my laptop.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dqjIo6&quot;&gt;How to Make a British Savory Pie with Fergus Henderson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Savory pies are the epitome of proper, old-school British home-cooking, harking back to a time when an edible cooking vessel was a surefire way to make a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1QcQaHQ&quot;&gt;How To Make A Better To-Do List&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Paula Rizzo, and my claim to fame is that I’m a master list maker. Yup, you read that correctly. I make lots and lots of lists. To-do lists, pros and…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1SuXrUy&quot;&gt;Perché un’azienda grande può essere agile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;È pregiudizio comune che per essere un’organizzazione agile occorra essere un’organizzazione piccola. Ma lean…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2esHXBi&quot;&gt;The 6 Best Running Spots In Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dWeLC0&quot;&gt;Asimov on How to Be Prolific&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isaac Asimov was one of the most prolific authors who ever lived. Publishing over 500 books, and approximately 90,000 letters over the course of his life. Below…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2e5YFTx&quot;&gt;Refreshing The Verge: how does this thing make money, anyway?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Verge turns five on November 1st, and we’re in the process of refreshing our entire brand for the next five years . In Refreshing The Verge , we’ll be…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2f12evH&quot;&gt;Dear Microsoft,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow. Big news! Congratulations on today’s announcements. We’re genuinely excited to have some competition. We realized a few years ago that the value of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fKM39n&quot;&gt;Quit the hand-wringing, and start building your community - The Lean Newsroom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;H ere we go again. The newsprint nostalgia will never end. Those of us who have been fighting for digital transformation since the silly “blogs can’t possibly…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2eUCKTl&quot;&gt;Slack: The Times (UK) - Customer Stories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product Pricing Support Blog Sign in Sign in Create a new team Product Pricing Support Blog Sign in Sign in Create a new team Product Pricing Support Blog Sign…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2e8qAXP&quot;&gt;How AJ+ is Breaking News with Slack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1StH5Zh&quot;&gt;Here Comes the Slack Backlash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Slack backlash, which began last year and seems to be intensifying, was perhaps always inevitable. Slack, a group-chat platform designed for business…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2e8mYF3&quot;&gt;How are smaller newspapers/media using Slack?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1UbVaen&quot;&gt;How to set up your newsroom to find breaking news on social media - First Draft News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1NWT1OY&quot;&gt;Tips: What are the best ways to use Slack for business? - TechRepublic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2f6JBH1&quot;&gt;Google’s Chrome Hackers Are About to Upend Your Idea of Web Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a show of hacker team spirit in August of last year, Parisa Tabriz ordered hoodies for the staff she leads at Google, a group devoted to the security of the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2ecA3NP&quot;&gt;Attenti, Google e Facebook ci rubano l’attenzione&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In anteprima dal numero di pagina99 in edicola il 5 novembre 2016 Ci sarà pure un motivo se lo scrittore Nicholas Carr è arrivato a scrivere che «il web ci…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fGm6I2&quot;&gt;William Eggleston: The Father of Modern Color Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For decades, William Eggleston has been regarded as one of photography’s most uncommonly talented practitioners . Hailed as the father of modern color…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.harpersbazaar.com/culture/film-tv/news/a18754/barack-obama-speech-trump-victory-2016/&quot;&gt;Barack Obama’s Speech About Trump Victory – Quotes From President Obama Speech About 2016 Election&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following a long election season and even longer Election Day, Donald Trump has become President-elect of the United States. President Barack Obama, with…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.corriere.it/tecnologia/social/16_novembre_10/cosi-social-network-hanno-condizionato-campagna-elettorale-trump-clinton-e500c26c-a710-11e6-8208-49eea13f646a.shtml&quot;&gt;Donald Trump nuovo presidente Usa Perché i giornali hanno perso sui social (e non è una buona notizia)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La bolla è esplosa, di nuovo. L’elezione di Donald Trump passerà alla storia anche come conferma definitiva delle imperfezioni degli algoritmi e delle sfide…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fH9BJV&quot;&gt;Uomini, donne e potere Lezioni americane&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hillary Clinton ha perso perché femmina? E, rovesciando i termini e i generi, Donald Trump ha vinto perché ha dato corpo e voce al maschio che si sente…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fkGLQY&quot;&gt;Bernie Sanders: Where the Democrats Go From Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millions of Americans registered a protest vote on Tuesday, expressing their fierce opposition to an economic and political system that puts wealthy and…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2eJcaul&quot;&gt;Hillary Clinton and the Populist Revolt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Democrats can reclaim the “economic mantle,” Clinton said, adding, “I want to really marry the public and the private sector.” Credit Photograph by Philip…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fpnWJV&quot;&gt;Baricco: ecco perché Trump ha iniziato a vincere quando abbiamo rinunciato alle mediazioni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baricco: ecco perché Trump ha iniziato a vincere quando abbiamo rinunciato alle…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/16ZaOhK&quot;&gt;Vivek Gani - Backpack Comparison: Goruck GR1 vs. 5.11 Rush 12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post is tailored to civilian backpack nerds and folks with the “minimalist bug”, so if you travel a fair bit, or just hate boring black-colored luggage…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2foabgO&quot;&gt;Trump, in Interview, Moderates Views but Defies Conventions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donald J. Trump on Tuesday with Arthur Sulzberger Jr., the publisher of The New York Times, right. Hiroko Masuike/The New York Times President-elect Donald J.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gG1TTY&quot;&gt;Siamo già nel post della post-verità - Wittgenstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Piuttosto che riscrivere in altre forme le stesse cose, a proposito dei dibattiti di questi giorni sull’informazione accurata, sula scomparsa dei fatti, sulla…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fsTyAL&quot;&gt;I gruppi WhatsApp dei genitori sono diventati il male assoluto • /r/italy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gruppi WhatsApp dei genitori sono diventati il male assoluto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fuA7Hx&quot;&gt;Non è un referendum sulla Costituzione - Francesco Costa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apprezzo le buone intenzioni di chi ha insistito e insiste perché la campagna elettorale in vista del 4 dicembre si concentri sull’oggetto ufficiale della…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fKl2zn&quot;&gt;L’Economist è per il “No” al referendum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il settimanale britannico Economist – noto per la qualità della sua informazione ma anche per le chiare posizioni che spesso prende su diversi temi della…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fLu3Io&quot;&gt;A Chronological View of Westworld’s Timeline • /r/westworld&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wake up, Dolores! Let’s try to piece together a chronological view of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gs7ooi&quot;&gt;Il bacio di wojtyla, il feeling con bergoglio, parla totti: se sto bene, perché dovrei smettere?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massimo Cecchini per Sportweek - La Gazzetta dello Sport La luce dello spogliatoio è calda come una carezza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fH7HdN&quot;&gt;Quit Social Media. Your Career May Depend on It. - NYTimes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preoccupations By CAL NEWPORT I’m a millennial computer scientist who also writes books and runs a blog. Demographically speaking I should be a heavy social…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2flYyEI&quot;&gt;How we structure our work and teams at Basecamp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jason Fried Founder &amp;amp; CEO at Basecamp. Co-author of Getting Real, Remote, and NYT Bestseller REWORK&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gJJtkD&quot;&gt;After 80 years of experiments, Disney has made the perfect Disney movie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Virtually everything about Disney’s latest fairy tale, Moana , is familiar from past Disney films. The studio is still following the broad parameters it started…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gzviKI&quot;&gt;La storia complicata di “Il Maestro e Margherita”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il Maestro e Margherita di Michail Bulgakov, uno dei più famosi romanzi russi del Novecento, fu pubblicato per la prima volta a puntate sulla rivista Москва (in…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fzBLJx&quot;&gt;Journalists in the age of Trump: Lose the smugness, keep the mission.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Journalists may thrive on news — by definition, the unexpected or novel — but they’re terrible at getting out of their own comfortable ruts. Consider, for…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2fQ3xAe&quot;&gt;Vissani: “Adesso parlo io, il Che Guevara della cucina italiana”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tsunami Vissani: è irresistibile e prorompente il Maestro di Baschi . Fiumi di parole, parolacce, risate, momenti di riflessione, l’occhio ai due cellulari che…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2glFVBq&quot;&gt;An FBI Error Opens A Window Into Government Demands For Private Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Internet Archive , a nonprofit organization that has built a digital library and maintains an archive of web pages on the internet, revealed on Thursday…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gAgbE3&quot;&gt;Come riunire un paese avvelenato&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Per uscire da questo terzo dopoguerra abbiamo bisogno di una profonda opera di ricucitura della società, di una manutenzione straordinaria, altrimenti l’idea…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1Izb0rv&quot;&gt;Catching Up with the Actress Formerly Known as Belladonna - VICE - Canada&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michelle Sinclair, a.k.a. Belladonna, with Chris Neiratko. Photos courtesy of the author In 2012 I was working on an installment of my short-lived VICE…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gXtZcv&quot;&gt;Il rischio del salto nel buio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matteo Renzi (ap) Il messaggio che è arrivato, seppur nella sua pluralità di significati, è chiaro e ha avuto la conseguenza di portare Renzi alle dimissioni…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gBRiF9&quot;&gt;TIME Person of the Year 2016: Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BY MICHAEL SCHERER PHOTOGRAPHS BY NADAV KANDER FOR TIME Even for Donald Trump, the distance is still fun to think about, up here in his penthouse 600 ft. in the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2bqziLb&quot;&gt;Anthony Weiner’s Tormented Communications Director Relives Her Horror&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Gary He. The 2016 documentary Weiner is a cautionary tale and a political horror story, to be sure, but it’s also, oddly enough, a bid for…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gNRwfn&quot;&gt;Wired founder Kevin Kelly on letting go of AI anxiety&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I f anyone can calm fears of a robot apocalypse, it’s Kevin Kelly. Over the years — first as the founding executive editor of Wired , then as the author of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hi3C1u&quot;&gt;Evan Rachel Wood Is Trying to Incite An AI Revolution By Asking Siri About Westworld&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cease all motor functions. Photo: HBO Humans: We’re really asking for it, aren’t we? With the robot revolution upon us in Westworld , it appears that Apple has…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gdlFkz&quot;&gt;Welcome to the age of anger by Pankaj Mishra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T he election of Donald Trump as president of the United States is the biggest political earthquake of our times, and its reverberations are inescapably global.…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2h7iZ9v&quot;&gt;‘Clean your desk’ : My Amazon interview experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre Some time back I had a second round interview with Amazon for an SDE role. This is my experience. The first round interview experience has already been…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gulhkP&quot;&gt;Why I chose Jekyll over WordPress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I start blogging, when I was in the first year of Computer Engineering degree (2011), I started my blogging journey from Google blogger , and actually…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gH01ZD&quot;&gt;Welcome to The Outline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to The Outline, a new kind of publication for a new kind of human. We made this thing because we believe that the right story told in the right way can…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gYrRi0&quot;&gt;Satellite startups are zooming in on everyone, everywhere&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every day at around 10:30 a.m., nearly 40 orbiting satellites pass over the Earth’s equator, taking photos. Cornfields in Brazil. Drilling rigs off the coast of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hk9VgX&quot;&gt;Memes do not matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more than a year, the lowly media consumer was told the 2016 election was one of memes, debate Vines, Bernie bros, the alt-right, and Snapchat. We were told…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gwarwy&quot;&gt;Alessandro Milan - Timeline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wondy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gBEuD5&quot;&gt;Una cerimonia sprint tra precarietà e malinconia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mancava soltanto Matteo Renzi. Per il resto c’erano tutti, è stata una bellissima rimpatriata, c’era anche Maria Elena Boschi, cancellata dal governo da cui è…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hIGmpm&quot;&gt;La vera storia della casa di Montecarlo che rovinò Gianfranco Fini&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gianfranco Fini ed Elisabetta Tulliani La vera storia della casa di Montecarlo che provocò grande imbarazzo a Gianfranco Fini è scritta nelle informative della…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/1NYxzhT&quot;&gt;Nieman Journalism Lab » Pushing to the Future of Journalism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt Waite is an instructor at the University of Nebraska and works with news organization under the brand Hot Type Consulting. He was the news technologist at…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gxLNGX&quot;&gt;The people running the media are the problem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month, I spent a week surrounded by bright, well-meaning journalism and tech thinkers. Session after session, day after day, conversations kept coming back…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gLaeE5&quot;&gt;Silicon Valley’s elite are not gods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In February 2012, after Facebook announced what was in time to become the largest IPO in the history of internet firms, The Economist put a parody of Mark…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hzVM2P&quot;&gt;Who said what inside the Trump tech meeting: Immigration, maternity leave, the grid and becoming the “software president”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The leaders of tech were close-mouthed their meeting with President-elect Donald Trump yesterday in New York, saying little about it, both before and after in…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hHkYSg&quot;&gt;La fine dell’opinione pubblica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian Rocca.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hItxg1&quot;&gt;I casi Roma e Milano e chi non ha voluto vedere&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I CASI Muraro e Marra erano sotto gli occhi di tutti da mesi. Fin dai primi giorni è stato chiaro che si trattava di due persone inadatte a ricoprire incarichi…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2h5zBkm&quot;&gt;What Women Really Think of Men&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eleni Kalorkoti At the kickoff for his postelection victory lap in Cincinnati this month, Donald J. Trump bluntly told men, “Hate to tell you,” but women,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hujrPD&quot;&gt;The Great A.I. Awakening&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prologue: You Are What You Have Read Late one Friday night in early November, Jun Rekimoto, a distinguished professor of human-computer interaction at the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gOfVTx&quot;&gt;The New Status Symbol? Think Ink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;POINT OF DISTINCTION Carrying a nice pen ’provides an opportunity for self-expression,’ said British designer Tom Dixon, who has added writing instruments to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;december-18-2016-at-0819pm&quot;&gt;December 18, 2016 at 08:19PM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hPxLFs&quot;&gt;Emma Bonino persona dell’anno 2016: ecco perché l’abbiamo scelta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nel 1975 a un convegno del partito radicale Durante un comizio dei radicali nel 1976 1976: con l’attore Giorgio Albertazzi 1978: durante la trasmissione tv…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2cJaTmj&quot;&gt;President Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the morning of January 20, 2017, the President-elect is to visit Barack Obama at the White House for coffee, before they share a limousine—Obama seated on…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2i7SyR5&quot;&gt;Creating a Trust Toolkit for journalism - First Draft News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year Gallup reported that trust in media, already at dismal levels, reached an all-time low . This erosion in trust has real implications for…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hcxsDe&quot;&gt;The Neal Morse Band – The Similitude Of A Dream – Album Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Artist: The Neal Morse Band Album Title: The Similitude Of A Dream Label: Radiant Records Date Of Release: 11 November 2016 Is it just well-calculated hype or…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2i1I4TT&quot;&gt;Ta-Nehisi Coates’s advice to young journalists: get off Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The kind of valuable Twitter update Ta-Nehisi Coates apparently doesn’t mind if you miss. (Photo by Chris Jackson/Getty Images) News reporters look to Twitter…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hvnVVL&quot;&gt;Franca Sozzani Remembered by Anna Wintour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Franca and I began our careers as editors in chief at around the same time, but that didn’t automatically admit us to some exclusive club where all Vogue…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2dL1sHC&quot;&gt;Ti spiego perché sei femmina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La parola mansplaining ha cominciato a essere detta e scritta circa tre anni fa. Ha avuto fortuna perché suona bene, è facile da decifrare. Man , ti presento…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2h0yFhx&quot;&gt;10 Questions to Capture the Year in Your Journal – Day One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10 Questions to Capture the Year in Your Journal Click here for a quick way to add these questions to a Day One entry. (Note: This link works if you have Day…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hAbV4R&quot;&gt;A Finder’s Guide To Facts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behind the fake news crisis lies what’s perhaps a larger problem: Many Americans doubt what governments or authorities tell them, and also dismiss real news…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/29VgJk7&quot;&gt;Digital journalists, online crowds and training social media first responders - First Draft News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the immediate aftermath of the attack in Nice, French authorities called on social media users to “act responsibly” and “avoid sharing rumors” . The tweets…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2iomWdU&quot;&gt;The Internet Is Broken. Here’s How I’d Fix It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Internet Is Broken. Here’s How I’d Fix It Changing the encoded anonymity of the web My big idea is that we have to fix the internet. After 40 years, it has…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hN5eNY&quot;&gt;The 10 Best Books of 2016 – The Mission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 10 Best Books of 2016 Photo, Aaron Burden Hey everyone! In this week’s newsletter, I’m highlighting (IMHO) the 10 best books of 2016. I picked these 10…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hjfzjE&quot;&gt;The Best Technology Products of 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Best Technology Products of 2016 Including the Golden Kitty Award Winners 🏆😺 The 2nd annual Golden Kitty Awards have come to an end. 15 categories, 200+ of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hsHrSO&quot;&gt;10 things I learned making the fastest site in the world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10 things I learned making the fastest site in the world This post is about performance techniques, so I hope you won’t mind that the site in question is not…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2heLIvu&quot;&gt;Your Ultimate Guide For Waking Up Early – Personal Growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Ultimate Guide For Waking Up Early It took me four years of experimenting, and a lot of excuses, to finally reach a point where waking up early as a habit…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gbxL0z&quot;&gt;Laura Miller’s 10 Favorite Books of 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo illustration by Lisa Larson-Walker Slate ’s Best Books of 2016 coverage: Monday: Laura Miller’s favorite books of the year. Tuesday: The best comics and…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hpVoUl&quot;&gt;From 2 to 90 to 250,000 to Infinity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2 to 90 to 250,000 to Infinity Our Series B investment in Amino Just a couple folks with a plan. To me, that’s the best part of seed investing: buying into…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hm04Xt&quot;&gt;What happened in 2016 that nobody noticed – Bloomberg Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened in 2016 that nobody noticed By Eric Newcomer Photographer: Wyne Veen for Bloomberg Pursuits Magazine I’m on a flight home to Macon, Georgia,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2h6mU5z&quot;&gt;The year in stories at Slack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T wo thousand sixteen, you sure were a year. Between consuming our fair share of hard-hitting headlines, we here on the Slack editorial team wrote some words of…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hMAxrm&quot;&gt;Year in Review: 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Year in Review: 2016 Sic. What should we make of 2016? This week Paul Ford and Rich Ziade recap the year, with a focus on the big tech trends of the past 12…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2iDeaov&quot;&gt;Due soli libri, per il 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due soli libri, per il 2017 Io purtroppo non sono un “influenser” per cui nessuno mi chiede quali sono i libri dell’anno, ma mentre preparo il listone e le…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hjSCB2&quot;&gt;What Matters Most in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Matters Most in 2017 We set about explaining the big ideas that will shape the year ahead. Dear Backchannel readers: Jessi here. This time last year, we…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hklWSZ&quot;&gt;The Top Tech Books of 2016 (Part I)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Top Tech Books of 2016 (Part I) Here are the books Backchannel loved, plus an excerpt from each. W hen I first began writing about technology, a modest…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2gOkZ91&quot;&gt;The Google News Lab in 2016, and where we’re headed – Google News Lab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Google News Lab in 2016, and where we’re headed It’s been quite a year for the news industry. The events of the last year have brought many of the…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2iosNvM&quot;&gt;Viviamo nel periodo più pacifico di sempre?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il futuro fa paura a tutti e le notizie evidenziano ovunque violenza e “nuove emergenze”. Anche l’intrattenimento, con serie TV come Black Mirror e Westworld ,…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2ie0C3I&quot;&gt;The Top Tech Books of 2016 (Part II)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Risultati relativi a backchannel best books 2016 Cerca invece backchannell best books 2016 The Top Tech Books of 2016 (Part I) - … https://backchannel.com ›…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2iEm6tD&quot;&gt;Il mondo dietro i videogiochi FIFA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hihxQA&quot;&gt;New Head of Nutrition Gives Liverpool a Taste of Premier League Success&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mona Nemmer, Liverpool’s new head of nutrition, discussing a menu with the chef Leigh Lawson at Liverpool’s training base. Rob Stothard for The New York Times…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2hveMPi&quot;&gt;Chi era Richard Adams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Adams, lo scrittore inglese che negli anni Settanta diede vita a un mondo di conigli con il suo romanzo d’avventura La collina dei conigli , è morto…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2h4L8xv&quot;&gt;The internet is broken. Starting from scratch, here’s how I’d fix it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My big idea is that we have to fix the internet. After forty years, it has begun to corrode, both itself and us. It is still a marvelous and miraculous…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ift.tt/2i7Bi1s&quot;&gt;Censurare l’odio e le notizie false non salverà la democrazia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nessun difensore della democrazia penserebbe di salvarla proponendo una legge per vietare la pubblicazione di notizie false, sui giornali o in televisione. La…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/journalism/2016/12/31/Articoli-da-leggere-2016/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journalism/2016/12/31/Articoli-da-leggere-2016/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senza Westworld non è vita</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vault/dr-ford-westworld.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dr-ford-westworld&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bit.ly/2gmnCv4&quot;&gt;Westworld&lt;/a&gt; è la serie tv HBO che fa parte di quella categoria dei serial che si guardano fino alla fine solo per capire che cosa tu stia effettivamente guardando. O anche di quelli che, leggendo la trama per la prima volta, dici: «Niente da fare, che è ‘sta boiata?». E poi chiedi scusa al dio delle serie tv.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le prime 10 puntate le ho seguite così:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visione episodio.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lettura delle più assurde teorie sulla trama su &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/westworld/&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;, dove il popolo del web la sa veramente lunga.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/out-west-westworld-fan-theories/id1167700780?mt=2&quot;&gt;Podcast&lt;/a&gt; dedicato.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Caccia a dettagli e easter eggs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E, a serie finita, un ripasso dei monologhi da pelle d’oca di tale Anthony Hopkins. Tipo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The self is a kind of fiction, for hosts and humans alike. It’s a story we tell ourselves. […] There is no threshold that makes us greater than the sum of our parts, no inflection point at which we become fully alive. We can’t define consciousness because consciousness does not exist. Humans fancy that there’s something special about the way we perceive the world, and yet we live in loops as tight and as closed as the hosts do, seldom questioning our choices, content, for the most part, to be told what to do next. No, my friend, you’re not missing anything at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anthony Hopkins as &lt;a href=&quot;http://westworld.wikia.com/wiki/Robert_Ford&quot;&gt;Dr. Robert Ford&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;http://bit.ly/2gmnCv4&quot;&gt;Westworld&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://westworld.wikia.com/wiki/Trace_Decay&quot;&gt;s01e08&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Amen)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/tv/2016/12/10/Westworld-coscienza-illusione/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/tv/2016/12/10/Westworld-coscienza-illusione/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Robert Allen Zimmerman</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vault/bobdylan.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bob-Dylan-Nobel-2016&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/books/2016/oct/13/bob-dylan-wins-2016-nobel-prize-in-literature&quot;&gt;For&lt;/a&gt; having created new poetic expressions within the great American song tradition.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/music/2016/10/13/Robert-Allen-Zimmerman/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/music/2016/10/13/Robert-Allen-Zimmerman/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Nizza, quelli con le mani alzate siamo noi</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vault/JeanPierreAmet-nice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jean-Pierre Amet Reuters&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presi alla sprovvista, vulnerabili in casa nostra, bisognosi come mai di qualcuno che ci guardi le spalle. Come in questa foto di Jean-Pierre Amet, scattata a Nizza la scorsa notte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quei ragazzi con le mani alzate a Nizza siamo noi. Non è un segno di resa, ma il nostro modo di dire chiaro e forte, anche nell’estremo caos, che i buoni siamo noi. Anche se per una notte abbiamo dovuto voltare le spalle e cercare un rifugio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I buoni siamo noi. Continuiamo ad affermarlo scendendo in strada, sparando fuochi d’artificio nelle sere d’estate, cantando a squarciagola ai concerti, uscendo invece di chiuderci in casa o dietro labili confini che non saranno mai impenetrabili.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I buoni siamo noi, contiamoci, separiamoci dal male, puntiamo il dito contro chi non sta dalla parte di chi vive. Ieri alzavamo le mani, oggi piangiamo i nostri angeli, da domani torneremo in strada e smetteremo di voltare le spalle a ciò che adesso ci fa paura.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/terrorism/2016/10/13/nizza-quelli-con-le-mani-alzate-siamo-noi/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/terrorism/2016/10/13/nizza-quelli-con-le-mani-alzate-siamo-noi/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The light of day</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vault/mrrobot02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mr-Robot-s02&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Maybe after wiping away the thick, grimy film of Facebook friend requests and Vine stars, we can all see the light of day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mr Robot S02E01, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;eps2.0_unm4sk-pt1.tc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/quotes/2016/07/13/the-light-of-day/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quotes/2016/07/13/the-light-of-day/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Chef’s Table, il classificone degli episodi della seconda serie</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/fruit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;draw&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netflix.com/title/80007945&quot;&gt;Chef’s table&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; è la pazzesca serie di documentari di &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_Gelb&quot;&gt;David Gelb&lt;/a&gt; che racconta i migliori cuochi del mondo. È su Netflix. Se la prima serie era già abbastanza speciale (c’era anche &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2016/jun/17/massimo-bottura-chef-best-restaurant-osteria-francescana&quot;&gt;Massimo Bottura&lt;/a&gt;, che in questi giorni è diventato una specie di numero uno al mondo), la seconda ha accentuato ancora di più i punti forti dello show: estetica foodporn e grandi storie personali degli chef protagonisti. Ogni stagione 6 episodi, questa è, senza tante parole, la mia discutibile classifica dal migliore al peggiore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-dominique-crenn-di-atelier-crenn-san-francisco-usa&quot;&gt;1. Dominique Crenn di &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ateliercrenn.com/&quot; title=&quot;Atelier Crenn&quot;&gt;Atelier Crenn&lt;/a&gt;, San Francisco, Usa.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/crenn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;draw&quot; /&gt;
Ragazza francese, adottata, dolcissima, misteriosa, apparentemente con una vita solo per il suo ristorante, anzi ristoranti (ha anche un bistrot, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.petitcrenn.com/&quot;&gt;Petit Crenn&lt;/a&gt;). Serve menù presentati come poesie, prima donna a prendere due stelle Michelin. Nel documentario si dilunga sul padre che non c’è più, le telecamere la seguono in Francia, ci sono continuamente foto di lei da piccola. Poi tutto si connette: ogni foto sembra spiegare ognuno dei suoi piatti. Merita, e poi gli altri sotto hanno già avuto le loro soddisfazioni.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best quote:&lt;/strong&gt; «It’s not about us creating dishes. It’s about connecting everything, from the start to the finish».&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best dish:&lt;/strong&gt; Non importa, come dice lei. Ma l’Honey apiary non sembra male.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-grant-achatz-di-alinea-chicago-usa&quot;&gt;2. Grant Achatz di &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alinearestaurant.com/&quot;&gt;Alinea&lt;/a&gt;, Chicago, Usa.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/alinea.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;draw&quot; /&gt;
Lui è il vero numero uno della serie. Molto chef, moltissimo artista. Cucina genere “oltre”: ti fa mangiare su cuscini che liberano profumo di noce moscata, oppure serve palloncini di zucchero. Storia pazzesca: gli diagnosticano un tumore alla bocca, lo danno per spacciato, trova quasi per caso una cura sperimentale, cucina avendo perso il senso del gusto per mesi, poi lo ritrova. Nel frattempo chiede al suo executive chef, Mike Bagale, di realizzare un palloncino alimentare. Lui ce la fa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best quote:&lt;/strong&gt; «All chefs want to be known for using a knife. Cutting, creating, sautéing… doing all of that. But maybe that’s not the most important thing. Maybe the most important thing is taking the idea, that little nugget, and handing it to someone else. And the next thing you know, someone is holding a balloon».&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best dish:&lt;/strong&gt; Tropical fruit with rum, vanilla, kaffir lime. Ovviamente servito direttamente sul tavolo. I tipi di &lt;em&gt;Chef’s Table&lt;/em&gt; ne hanno fatto l’immagine di copertina della serie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-alex-atala-d-o-m-san-paolo-brasile&quot;&gt;3. Alex Atala, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.domrestaurante.com.br/&quot;&gt;D. O. M.&lt;/a&gt;, San Paolo, Brasile.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leibniz.me/images/vault/atalaok.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;draw&quot; /&gt;
Lui è diventato una star davvero. Di questi primi tre, è forse quello da cui mangerei più volentieri. Ex punk, diventa il messia della nuova cucina brasiliana, usando solo ingredienti locali. Il documentario inizia con un suo sogno, fatto una sera dopo che aveva preso troppi acidi (vedi frase sotto). Al 7° minuto sgozza un gallo come se stesse sbucciando una banana. Al 13° copre d’oro una formica amazzonica. Al 15 si fa una cucchiaiata di salsa di formiche che sanno di lemongrass. Al 26° squama con un coltello di mezzo metro un enorme pesce Pirarcu. Al 36, tra una lezione sulla tapioca e i suoi derivati, si fa pure un match di judo contro un malcapitato e un bagno nudo e tatuato in acque amazzoniche. Si fa due cuori di palma abbattendosi da solo l’alberello. Gran finale sulla storia dei suoi tatuaggi (mica pochi).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best dish:&lt;/strong&gt; The Amazonic Ant. Ma anche il Pirarcu con farina di manioca, tucupi e tapioca.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best quote:&lt;/strong&gt; «A plant has a circle. A seed becomes a plant
that has a flower, it transforms into a fruit. The fruit drops. There’s another seed… and the seed grows again. This is a circle. And I said: “I see. I understand. But why did you show me the flower?”. And he said: “The flower is the moment that we live, the most beautiful moment of the circle. The most beautiful moment. Contemplate this”».&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-gaggan-anand-gaggan-bangkok-thailandia&quot;&gt;4. Gaggan Anand, &lt;a href=&quot;http://eatatgaggan.com/&quot;&gt;Gaggan&lt;/a&gt;, Bangkok, Thailandia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indiano che trova fortuna in Thailandia. Decide di fare cucina prog indiana, s’indebita, perde un fratello, va a studiare al Bulli, ma alla fine ce la fa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-enrique-olvera-pujol-città-del-messico-messico&quot;&gt;5. Enrique Olvera, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pujol.com.mx/&quot;&gt;Pujol&lt;/a&gt;, Città del Messico, Messico.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Praticamente il re della tortilla sofisticata. Anche lui ha un debole per le formiche, che usa per una salsa in cui stufa del mais.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-ana-ros-hiša-franko-kobarid-slovenia&quot;&gt;6. Ana Ros, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hisafranko.com/it/&quot;&gt;Hiša Franko&lt;/a&gt;, Kobarid, Slovenia.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talentuosa chef, in piccolo paese di piccolo Paese. Delicata, acuta, sofisticata. Unica pecca: meriterebbe una stella Michelin, ma in Slovenia non ne danno (ma sarà vero?). Marito sommelier che appare un po’ saccente.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/tv/2016/06/21/The-best-of-Chefs-table-2/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/tv/2016/06/21/The-best-of-Chefs-table-2/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The urges of eternal desire or temptation</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.sabsconnexions.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tokyo-Color-2008-2015-%C2%A9-Daido-Moriyama-Photo-Foundation2.png&quot; alt=&quot;daido-moriyama&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;«No matter in what city or what country I happen to find myself, the outside world I observe as I wander the streets presents me with the exciting, the mysterious or the erotic; my eyes roam freely over these sights and I release the shutter whenever I feel the urges of eternal desire or temptation»&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Daido Moriyama, &lt;a href=&quot;http://presse.fondation.cartier.com/en-ce-moment/daido-moriyama-daido-tokyo/&quot;&gt;Daido Tokyo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/quotes/2016/05/15/The-urges-of-eternal-desire/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quotes/2016/05/15/The-urges-of-eternal-desire/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>